
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
      <title>Outline Changelog</title>
      <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog</link>
      <description>New updates and improvements to Outline. Follow us on twitter @getoutline to find out when features are released.</description>
      <language>en</language>
      <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="https://www.getoutline.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      
  <item>
    <guid>image-resizing</guid>
    <title>Resizable images</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/image-resizing</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Resizing images in Outline" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/resizing-images.gif"/></p><p>It is now possible to resize images in Outline. This is a feature that has been
requested for a long time and we&#x27;re excited to finally ship another foundational
feature.</p><p>When editing simply drag the handles on the image to change the size. Images snap to a
grid to help in alignment.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>code-line-numbers</guid>
    <title>Code block line numbers</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/code-line-numbers</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Code block line numbers" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/code-line-numbers.png"/></p><p>Code blocks in documents are now displayed with dynamic line numbers by default, if you prefer they can be disabled through a new setting found in user preferences.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>multiple-workspaces</guid>
    <title>Multiple workspaces</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/multiple-workspaces</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>We&#x27;re excited to announce that you can now create multiple workspaces to support different departments, or organizations with the same SSO login methods.</p><p>Workspaces are currently billed and managed separately and are available in the workspace switcher in the top left of the app or through the command menu.</p><p><img alt="New Outline workspace" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/new-workspace.png"/></p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>diff-view</guid>
    <title>Visualizing document history</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/diff-view</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>From today we&#x27;re now able to display a rich &quot;diff&quot; of what has changed in a document
since it was last edited. You&#x27;ll see this view in email notifications <em>and</em> when navigating
through the document history sidebar…</p><p><strong>Tip:</strong> You can quickly open the history sidebar by clicking on the last edited timestamp.</p><p><img alt="Outline email notification" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/diff-view.jpeg"/></p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>upgradable-viewers</guid>
    <title>Upgradable viewers</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/upgradable-viewers</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Since the launch of <a href="/changelog/viewer-permissions">viewer permissions</a> we&#x27;ve heard requests for a need for increased flexibility.
As of today it&#x27;s now possible to upgrade the permissions of workspace viewers in individual collections.</p><p>Simply add the viewer member to a collection and change their permission to &quot;View and edit&quot; the same as you might a regular member.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>document-subscriptions</guid>
    <title>Document subscriptions</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/document-subscriptions</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Sometimes you want to keep an eye on a document without having to open it, or you want to be notified when a document is updated. You can now subscribe to documents to receive notifications when they are updated by other team members. To subscribe to any document, click the &quot;Subscribe&quot; button in any document menu or access through the command menu with <code>cmd</code>+<code>k</code> on macOS. (<code>ctrl</code>+<code>k</code> on Windows/Linux).</p><p><img alt="Document subscriptions" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/document-subscriptions.png"/></p><p>You will automatically be subscribed to a document when you create or edit it, but you can unsubscribe at any time.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>personal-gmail-signin</guid>
    <title>Sign-in with Gmail</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/personal-gmail-signin</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>We&#x27;ve been working hard behind the scenes to make authentication more flexible for teams following on from <a href="/changelog/team-domains">team domain restrictions</a>.</p><p>It is now possible to sign-in to your Outline account with a personal Gmail account if you have already been invited to the matching email address.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>mermaid-diagrams</guid>
    <title>Mermaid diagrams</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/mermaid-diagrams</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>We&#x27;re excited to have full support for <a href="https://mermaid-js.github.io/">Mermaid</a> diagrams in Outline. Mermaid is a simple markdown-like syntax for generating diagrams and flowcharts from text. It&#x27;s a great way to add diagrams of all types directly in your documentation.</p><p>You can insert a Mermaid diagram directly into a document by using the /mermaid slash command or by setting the code block language to &quot;Mermaid Diagram&quot;.</p><p>Here&#x27;s an example of a flowchart:</p><p><img alt="Mermaid diagram" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/mermaid-diagram-source.png"/></p><p>Which renders as:</p><p><img alt="Mermaid diagram" src="/images/mermaid-diagram.png"/></p><p>For full documentation on all the syntax and types of graphs that can be created be sure to check out the <a href="https://mermaid-js.github.io/mermaid/#/">Mermaid documentation</a>.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>may-fixes</guid>
    <title>May fixes and improvements</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/may-fixes</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Another catchup of improvements and fixes from May that haven&#x27;t been covered in
larger updates, we&#x27;re always working on making the app faster and more reliable…</p><ul><li>Lots of backend performance improvements to improve loading speeds, particularly for large collections</li><li>When importing a document a revision is now written immediately so that it can be restored to the imported state</li><li>Suspended users are no longer shown as collaborators on documents they&#x27;ve previously edited</li><li>The submit button is now focused by default in confirmation dialogs</li><li>We improved the user matching of searches from Slack</li><li>Links with in-page anchors are no longer broken when a document is renamed</li><li>Emoji&#x27;s and embeds are now copied to the clipboard correctly when copying document text</li><li>Formatting toolbar now appears only once the mouse is released</li><li>Improved search indexing for publicy shared documents</li><li>Secondary clicking a link in the editor no longer causes it to open</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>team-domains</guid>
    <title>Team domain restrictions</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/team-domains</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="team domain restrictions" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/team-domains.png"/></p><p>This week brings two new security settings. It&#x27;s now possible to restrict all sign-ups
to your team to a specific domain name through &quot;Allowed domains&quot;. This setting applies in <em>addition</em> to
SSO and will disallow users from creating accounts that do not have a confirmed
matching email domain.</p><p>We also added the ability to restrict sign-ups through SSO completely, so that
users must first be invited by an admin. Both of these new settings can be found
under <strong>Settings</strong> -&gt; <strong>Security</strong>.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>april-fixes</guid>
    <title>April fixes and improvements</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/april-fixes</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Here we go – a big grab-bag of other improvements and fixes from April that we wanted to make sure
the community is aware of…</p><ul><li>Dropping files into a document now works more reliably</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to manually resend outstanding invites</li><li>Link previews and search now work inside collection descriptions</li><li><code>cmd</code>+<code>n</code> browser shortcut to open a new window no longer creates a new document</li><li>It&#x27;s now much easier to create inline code marks</li><li>Fixed an issue that meant you could not share a search results page</li><li>The disabled state of document embeds now persists between reloads</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to fetch a document from the API without knowing its full slug</li><li>Fixed an issue where collection names with slashes would produce an invalid export</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>turkish-translations</guid>
    <title>Turkish translations</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/turkish-translations</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Thanks to a community member <a href="https://crowdin.com/profile/EmirDEV">Emir</a> this week
brings application-wide Turkish translations 🇹🇷. If your system is set to this language
we&#x27;ll automatically suggest switching Outline&#x27;s language to match, or you can go
to Settings -&gt; Profile -&gt; Language to update.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>tldraw-embed</guid>
    <title>Tldraw embed</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/tldraw-embed</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="tldraw embed" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/tldraw-embed.png"/></p><p>Thanks to an open source contributor <a href="https://github.com/Limezy">Limezy</a>, we now
have support for interactive tldraw embeds. These look really fantastic inside
Outline and allow multiple people to draw together inside a document.</p><p>To get started head to <a href="https://www.tldraw.com">tldraw.com</a>, click on the
cursors icon in the top left and select &quot;Create a Multiplayer Project&quot; – paste
the url into an Outline doc.</p><p><img alt="How to enable tldraw" src="/images/tldraw-enable.png"/></p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>april-new-embeds</guid>
    <title>JSFiddle, Gliffy, and Otter.ai embeds</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/april-new-embeds</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="JSFiddle embed" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/new-embeds.png"/></p><p>This week brings three new integrations – just paste a share link in any
document to get a rich, interactive, embed.</p><ul><li><a href="https://jsfiddle.net/">JSFiddle</a> – an online IDE for writing and testing code snippets (&quot;fiddles&quot;) in the browser.</li><li><a href="https://www.gliffy.com/">Gliffy</a> – an enterprise diagramming tool for creating flow charts, database diagrams, and wireframes.</li><li><a href="https://otter.ai/">Otter.ai</a> – allows interactive annotated meeting notes to be embedded in documents.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>shared-document-search</guid>
    <title>Shared documents now include search</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/shared-document-search</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Search input" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/shared-document-search.png"/></p><p>If you publicly share a document with nested document sharing enabled we&#x27;ll now display a
search input at the top of the sidebar to allow searching the contents of
all of the nested documents.</p><p>This is particularly great when sharing documentation and other larger collections
of docs.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>date-time-commands</guid>
    <title>New date slash commands</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/date-time-commands</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline date time commands" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/date-time-commands.gif"/></p><p>We added some new slash commands to insert the current date, time, or both into a document
you&#x27;re editing – and importantly these commands also work in document titles and
are locale-aware! These are the new handy shortcuts:</p><ul><li><code>/date</code> – Insert current date</li><li><code>/time</code> – Insert current time</li><li><code>/datetime</code> – Insert current date and time</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>star-collections</guid>
    <title>Collections can now be starred</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/star-collections</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline sidebar with starred collections" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/star-collections.png"/></p><p>Just like documents, collections can now be starred – once starred you can also
re-order all of your stars with drag and drop to create your own custom sidebar.
Star the things that are important to <em>you</em> and have them available for one-click
access.</p><p><strong>Tip:</strong> Did you know that adding an emoji in front of a document title will show it
in the browser favicon and in the sidebar when starred?</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>disable-collection-create</guid>
    <title>New option to disable collection creation</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/disable-collection-create</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Disable collection setting" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/disable-collection-creation.png"/></p><p>Admin&#x27;s now have a new option to disable creation of new collection by members,
for more curated knowledge bases or larger teams this can help prevent documentation
sprawling unchecked.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>command-bar-settings</guid>
    <title>Settings in command bar</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/command-bar-settings</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline command bar settings" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/command-bar-settings.png"/></p><p>It&#x27;s now possible to access all the settings screen directly from the command bar.
You can access the command bar anywhere in the app using <code>Cmd</code> + <code>k</code>, or
<code>Cmd</code> + <code>Shift</code> + <code>k</code> if you&#x27;re in the document editor.</p><p>If you&#x27;ve not used the command bar yet, it&#x27;s a fast way to access lots of
functionality without taking your hands off the keyboard!</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>file-attachments</guid>
    <title>File attachments</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/file-attachments</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline file attachments" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/file-attachments.png"/></p><p>We&#x27;re excited to finally add one of our most requested features – file attachments
in documents. You can now upload arbitrary files and embed them directly into
a doc for your teammates to download, file attachments work on publicly
shared links too.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>fit-and-finish</guid>
    <title>Fit and finish</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/fit-and-finish</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Mosaic" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/fit-and-finish.png"/></p><p>This months shipped improvements are lots of small details, alignments, bug fixes, and editor improvements. In the background we have been busy building long-awaited file attachments and search for publicly shared documents, both of which will be shipped in the next month.</p><h3>Fixes &amp; Improvements</h3><h4>Editor</h4><ul><li>Table of contents is now available on mobile</li><li>Improved positioning and editing around images in documents</li><li>We improved the default paragraph spacing</li><li>Pasted content from Dropbox Paper is now more accurately preserved</li><li>Document title no longer allows eronuously pasting rich text</li><li>Improved the behavior of links and link editing</li><li>External links now show an icon</li><li>Added support for domain-restricted Vimeo embeds</li><li>Fixed a bug that caused todo items to not show as checked in Firefox</li><li>Tabbing no longer escapes the editor</li></ul><h4>Platform</h4><ul><li>Collections can now be expanded and collapsed independently</li><li>It is now possible to move a nested document to the collection root by drag and dropping onto the collection</li><li>Fixed a number of bugs with import and exporting of documents</li><li>Fixed a bug where virus scanning software would scan magic links and make it impossible to sign-in</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to choose a default &quot;Home&quot; collection for your team</li><li>Performance, design, and various &quot;fit and finish&quot; improvements</li><li>Fixed a bug where some buttons would display unstyled in Safari</li><li>Collections with only drafts no longer show as empty</li><li>It&#x27;s no longer possible to see &quot;Never viewed&quot; on a document you created</li><li>Dangerous menu items now display in a different color</li><li>Reduced code loading on publicly shared links</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>pin-to-home</guid>
    <title>Pin to Home</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/pin-to-home</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Pin to home" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/pin-to-home.png"/></p><p>This month pinned documents got some love – a visual refresh to help them stand out, the ability to reorder, and also you can now pin documents to the home screen for everyone in the team to see. This year we&#x27;ll be focusing more on improving the options to customize and theme Outline and so this is a first step in that direction.</p><h3>Fixes &amp; Improvements</h3><ul><li>Drafts are now displayed in the sidebar while viewing and editing</li><li>Added ability to &quot;follow&quot; another user in a document by clicking their avatar</li><li>Added &quot;full width&quot; option for documents display</li><li>Added recent searches to search screen</li><li>New icons for collections</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to replace images in editor</li><li>You can now choose which events publish to Slack</li><li>🇻🇳 Vietnamese added as a language option</li><li>Lots of fixes in the editor and mobile support particularly</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>command-bar</guid>
    <title>Command Bar</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/command-bar</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline command bar" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/command-bar.png"/></p><p>This release also includes new <code>cmd</code>+<code>k</code> functionality which you might recognize from other productivity apps. Type <code>cmd</code>+<code>k</code> anywhere in the app to quickly move around your knowledge base! </p><p>We&#x27;ll be building all of the possible actions into this menu over the next few months, but try searching for docs, collections, or changing the theme to see how fun and easy it is to use!</p><h3>Fixes &amp; Improvements</h3><ul><li>Added Perl language support in editor code blocks</li><li>Public share links now include an option to change light/dark theme</li><li>It is now possible to set a default role for new users in Settings -&gt; Security</li><li>Warning when dragging doc between collections with different permissions</li><li>Zooming images now possible while editing</li><li>Several new icons for collections</li><li>It is now possible to delete previous exports in admin</li><li>🇵🇱 Polish added as language option</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>emoji-picker</guid>
    <title>A new integrated emoji picker</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/emoji-picker</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline emoji picker" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/emoji-picker.png"/></p><p>The editor gained a new emoji picker this month, just type &quot;:&quot; and a search term 
to quickly find relevant emojis for your document!</p><p>It&#x27;s now also possible to set a &quot;default role&quot; for new users that join your knowledge
base. For example, new signups can now have viewer priviledges by default. You can
find this setting under Settings -&gt; Security.</p><h3>Fixes and improvements</h3><h4>Editor</h4><ul><li>Fixed home key/keycombo not working correctly in headers</li><li><code>mailto:</code> links are supported in the editor again</li><li>Fixed issue where documents beginning with an emoji would overlay the table of contents</li><li>Clicking outside the editor will now always close an open toolbar</li><li>Creating newlines from a collapsed heading now behaves more predictably</li><li>Performance improvements to the editor</li></ul><h4>Platform</h4><ul><li>Customers that have a custom domain no longer show a &quot;Back to website&quot; link on the login screen</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to change the light/dark theme on publicly shared documents</li><li>You can now delete previous export data. By default these are still removed after 30 days.</li><li>Creating an API key no longer reloads the entire app</li><li>Context menus can no longer extend out of the available window space</li><li>The collection icon picker is now closable on mobile</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>polish-polish</guid>
    <title>Polish Language and Editor Improvements</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/polish-polish</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>The collaborative editing beta has been progressing well and we continue to let
it new teams. The last few weeks have largely been spent fixing and improving
this functionality for a broader launch, but some other things snuck in too…</p><h3>Fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Moving a document out of a private collection will now warn you of the new permissions</li><li>We added 6 new icons for collections</li><li>You can now also zoom images when editing a document, click once to select and again to zoom once selected</li><li>🇵🇱 Polish added as a user interface language option</li><li>Fixed active starred documents being highlighted twice in the sidebar</li><li>Fixed some occurances where a formatting toolbar could appear for an empty selection</li><li>Headings and code blocks are now togglable in the editor</li><li>The formatting toolbar now includes list options</li><li>Lists can now start at numbers other than 1 🙈</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>collaborative-editing</guid>
    <title>Collaborative Editing Beta</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/collaborative-editing</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="collaborative editing" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/collaborative-editing.png"/></p><p>This week we’re beginning to accept teams into the beta of collaborative editing,
this feature will allow multiple team members to edit the same document at the same
time, opening much wider range of use cases! It also lays the foundation for all
sorts of new features such as commenting.</p><p>If your team would like to participate please reach out to <a href="mailto:hello@getoutline.com">hello@getoutline.com</a>.</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Starred documents are now displayed in the sidebar</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to choose a user permission up-front when inviting</li><li>Exporting data no longer emails the result and is much more reliable</li><li>Lists can now start at numbers other than 1.</li><li>Improved compatability of <a href="/integrations/google-docs">Google Drive integration</a></li><li>The &quot;Share&quot; button now always appears, even when public sharing is disabled</li><li>There is a new menu for switching between signed in teams</li><li>Added Google Calendar embed support</li><li>Added <a href="/integrations/diagrams">Diagrams.net</a> embed support</li><li>Added 4 new collection icons</li><li>Fixed a race condtion in image upload that could result in errors</li><li>Fixed single row tables breaking on reload</li><li>Lots of new translations</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>tasks-and-history</guid>
    <title>Task lists and improved history</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/tasks-and-history</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="task list" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/task-list.png"/></p><h3>Task lists</h3><p>You&#x27;ve been able to create a task list or a checkbox list in Outline for a while,
but this week brings a nice improvement - we added task summaries so you can see 
how many tasks a doc contains and how many are completed without even opening it!</p><p>This is great for simple checklists such as new employee onboarding or a release
checklist that you wouldn&#x27;t neccesarily put in an issue tracker. You can also create
repetitive task lists in templates.</p><h3>Document history improvements</h3><p>The history sidebar was rebuilt to shows more than just edits, it now also includes archive,
delete, publish, moves, and other events that happen during the document&#x27;s lifetime.</p><p>You can find the new sidebar by clicking on the last edited timestamp or under &quot;History&quot; in the
document menu.</p><p><img alt="document history" src="/images/document-history.png"/></p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>We&#x27;ve made a number of server-side performance improvements</li><li>The &quot;Home&quot; tab now defaults to show recently viewed documents</li><li>Fixed an issue that potentially suppressed email notifications for document edits</li><li>Fixed the templates page erroring when scrolled</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>summer-2021</guid>
    <title>Summer Release</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/summer-2021</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Wow, another month has passed, here&#x27;s a quick update on what&#x27;s changed since June,
as is often the case as well as the big stuff we&#x27;ve been working on a lot of &quot;little details&quot;<br/>that make the daily experience better but aren&#x27;t always immediately visible.</p><h3>Improved search abilities</h3><p>We&#x27;re now tracking all the previous titles that a document has had to improve search
results and increase the liklihood of surfacing the right document, even if you can&#x27;t
<em>quite</em> remember what it&#x27;s latest title is.</p><h3>Collapsible headings</h3><p>We brought back the ability to collapse sections of a document under headings – simply
hover over any heading to see a new control to collapse the contents. Your preference is 
stored locally and is not seen by other team members that view the document.</p><p><img alt="Collapsible headings" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/collapsible-headings.gif"/></p><h3>Drag and drop to archive or delete</h3><p>You can now drag and drop documents from the sidebar directly into the archive or trash,
similar to how you would move or reorder. There&#x27;s a cute animation included to let you
know what will happen too.</p><p><img alt="Drag to archive" src="/images/drag-to-archive.png"/></p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Lots more translation hooks were added, we&#x27;re very close to 100% coverage so that the entirety of the UI can appear in the language of your choice.</li><li>Added access to the Table of Contents on mobile</li><li>Fixed an issue where the star option would appear for templates</li><li>Fixed the &quot;publish&quot; button being disabled on drafts when not editing them</li><li>Added new language options – Persian and Japanese 🌏</li><li>Added support for <a href="https://datastudio.google.com/">Google DataStudio</a> embeds</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>friendly-collections</guid>
    <title>Friendly Collection URLs</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/friendly-collections</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Friendly collection url" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/friendly-url.png"/></p><p>This week we&#x27;ve shipped lots of little improvements, one thing you might notice is that collections in Outline no longer have a long <code>UUID</code> in the address bar, instead you&#x27;ll see a shortened id and a friendly
version of the collection name. Not only is this nicer to look at, but it also makes quickly returning to
collections via searching in the address bar much easier!</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Application size was decreased by several hundred KB</li><li>Shortcut for toggling the Table of Contents was changed to <code>ctrl</code>+<code>alt</code>+<code>h</code></li><li>New language option – Portugêse (Brazil) 🇧🇷</li><li>Copying a share link to clipboard no longer includes dark mode styles when pasting into another rich editor</li><li>Fixed alignment of items in &quot;New from template&quot; menu</li><li>Fixed an issue where two <code>Restore</code> options would appear on a deleted document that was previously archived</li><li>Fixed background color of select inputs in dark mode on non-Mac platforms</li><li>Improved the performance of loading share links for documents with many attachments</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>public-sharing-improvements</guid>
    <title>Sharing Improvements</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/public-sharing-improvements</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline Public Sharing" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/public-sharing-improvements.png"/></p><p>Last week brings some great improvements to public document sharing. We recently simplified the sharing dialog to a popover and now added the ability to share an entire tree of nested documents too. This much-requested feature is great for sharing structured help docs or several related documents with a single link!</p><p>As an additional security measure the Share button will also display a globe icon if a document is shared publicly because one of it&#x27;s parents has been shared.</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Images now show a Download button for easy downloading of images in a document</li><li>In the share dialog see when the link was last accessed</li><li>Improved behavior when typing words that include underscores in the editor</li><li>Improved behavior with the cursor around the edges of inline code</li><li>Added support for <a href="https://www.descript.com/">Descript</a> embeds</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>viewer-details</guid>
    <title>Document Insights</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/viewer-details</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="viewer details" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/viewer-popover.png"/></p><p>We&#x27;ve rolled out a number of UI improvements in the past couple of weeks within documents. It&#x27;s now possible
to see who on your team has viewed a document, simply click on the <strong>&quot;Viewed by X people&quot;</strong> text beneath the
title for a detailed flyover of everyone that has viewed and when.</p><p>The pile of faces at the top right of a document continues to show who has previously <em>edited</em> or is active right now.
We&#x27;ll be adding more detailed team-level insights soon!</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Added print &quot;page break&quot; functionality to editor to adjust print layout (Insert via slash menu)</li><li>Permissions-policy header to disable <a href="https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/03/googles-floc-terrible-idea">FLOC</a> is now returned on all pages</li><li>Document content now takes up more horizontal space on larger screens</li></ul><h4>Fixes</h4><ul><li>Fixed content appearing behind status bar in iOS PWA on some models of iPhone</li><li>Moving a duplicated document from a private to a not-private collection now updates the permissions of it&#x27;s attachments</li><li>Improved frontend support for importing doc, docx files</li><li>Slack &#x27;Post to channel&#x27; functionality now works without the requirement of using Slack SSO </li><li>Page no longer reloads in Firefox when clicking some menu items</li><li>Removed extra space on left side of page when printing in Firefox</li><li>Fixed print styles in dark mode</li><li>Improved editor image upload to remove flickering of image when the placeholder is replaced</li><li>Fixed document hover preview appearing behind subheadings</li><li>Fixed several smaller editor issues and crashes</li><li>Typing a word with underscores in the middle no longer creates italic text</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>microsoft-sso</guid>
    <title>Microsoft SSO</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/microsoft-sso</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Microsoft Sign In" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/microsoft-sso.png"/></p><p>We’re excited to finally add a new sign-in method, Microsoft! Whether you’re using
MS Teams, Education, or Office 365, you can now use your organization’s Microsoft
account to sign-in to Outline and build a knowledge base.</p><p>We’ll soon be working on adding Microsoft Teams integration to allow searching 
and accessing your Outline documents directly from chat too, just like Slack.</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Improvements to mobile styling and functionality</li><li>New &quot;Page break&quot; functionality allows splitting content across pages when printed</li><li>Sharing functionality got a new, faster, &quot;flyover&quot; view</li><li>Share links will now show when they were last accessed in the admin</li><li>The keyboard shortcut guide got a new splash of paint and filter functionality</li><li>Document content now expands to use more space on larger screens</li><li>We made a number of performance improvements so Outline got <em>even faster</em></li><li>As always, more translated screens</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>viewer-permissions</guid>
    <title>Collection Permissions &amp; Viewers</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/viewer-permissions</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="viewer permissions" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/viewer-permissions.png"/></p><p>In the last couple of weeks we&#x27;ve deployed two changes that together really improve
the permissions story in Outline. It&#x27;s now possible to make a user a &quot;viewer&quot; at 
the team level, meaning they will not be able to edit any collections or documents
at all.</p><p>We also added the option to make the default access level for a collection &quot;view only&quot;,
you can then select just a couple of team members to have edit permissions.</p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added the ability to drag and drop files into the collection screen</li><li>Improved and more comprehensive translations</li><li>Visual improvements to dark mode styling and mobile context menus</li><li>Added a /logout route to support SLO </li><li>When viewing a public share route while signed in with edit permissions an &quot;Edit&quot; button is now displayed</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Suspending a user now logs them out of any active sessions immediately</li><li>When a suspended user tries to sign in with email the situation is now explained more clearly to them</li><li>Fixed an error in the shares.info API endpoint when the user that originally creating share has been deleted</li><li>Fixed an issue with invisible list bullets in Firefox</li><li>Fixed a rare error when moving documents</li><li>Fixed embed support for Lucid Charts on the lucid.app domain</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>reorder-collections</guid>
    <title>Reordering Collections</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/reorder-collections</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Reordering collections in Outline" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/reorder-collections.jpg"/></p><p>Building on our sidebar improvements from the start of the year, it&#x27;s now possible to <a href="https://twitter.com/getoutline/status/1372943061894930432">reorder collections</a> in the sidebar as a team admin – changes to the sidebar are synced to all team members. We also added reordering of list items in documents with a new drag and drop handle or the handy <code>ALT+Up/Down</code> shortcut. </p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><h4>Platform</h4><ul><li>Private collections now show a &quot;Private&quot; badge next to the title</li><li>Enlarged the scrollable area in the sidebar for improved UX on small screens</li><li>Added Russian language <a href="https://translate.getoutline.com">translations</a></li><li>Document menus now include an &quot;Import document&quot; option to import as a sub-document</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to upload images into collection descriptions</li><li>When viewing documents in the trash, their images no longer show as broken</li><li>An error when search term includes the &quot;%&quot; character has been resolved</li><li>Fixed an issue where moving a document in a private collection would cause it to become uneditable until reload</li></ul><h4>Editor</h4><ul><li>Resolved some instances where an invalid selection would crash the editor</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to drag and drop images into the editor from the file system again</li><li>Sticky document title no longer moves position when the document is saving</li><li>Drop cursor is now visible in dark theme as a white line</li><li>Improved pasting behavior into editor, particularly with external HTML and Markdown</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>progressive-web-app</guid>
    <title>Progressive Web App</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/progressive-web-app</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline on macOS" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/pwa.png"/></p><p>This week brings PWA support to Outline, allowing you to install the app to your
desktop and dock in just a couple of seconds. We&#x27;ve been enjoying how lightweight
this install is while keeping the two best parts of a native app experience – an 
icon in the dock and a dedicated window. To try it out, head over to <a href="https://app.getoutline.com">the app</a>, signin, and 
<strong>hit the &quot;Install&quot; button that appears in the address bar</strong>.</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><h4>Platform</h4><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible edit the description of a collection inline.</li><li>We added the ability to disable sharing of individual collections.</li><li>The sidebar is now resizable, you can also grab the edge and drag it all the way to the left to collapse.</li><li>Newly created documents now sort to the top of manually organized collections.</li><li>The sidebar now automatically scrolls to ensure that the active item is kept visible.</li><li>When navigating to a collection the default tab now reflects the sidebar rather than a &quot;recently updated&quot; view.</li><li>Added total user counts to tabs on people management screen.</li><li>Added <a href="https://drawings.google.com">Google Drawings</a> Integration.</li><li>Unpublishing a document created by another user now puts it in your drafts, not theres.</li></ul><h4>Editor</h4><ul><li>Fixed highlighted text with link in dark mode is impossible to read</li><li>Fixed a case where it was possible to to keep the block menu open while formatting menus are also open</li><li>Editor <code>ctrl+x</code> shortcuts now work correctly on Windows</li><li><code>Shift+Enter</code> keys now split list items and create a newline</li><li><code>Shift+Enter</code> and <code>Tab</code> keys now behave as expected within code blocks</li><li>Fixed an issue where the text caret in an empty notice block is invisible</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>sidebar-improvements</guid>
    <title>New year, new sidebar</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/sidebar-improvements</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Last week we deployed a new version of the Outline sidebar – it looks very 
similar to before – but make no mistake it&#x27;s rebuilt from the ground up! With
this new foundation comes the ability to reorder and move documents with drag
and drop…</p><p><img alt="Re-ordering in Outline" title="@1x" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/sidebar-reorder.gif"/></p><p>…plus you can now collapse the sidebar entirely (<code>cmd+.</code> is the handy shortcut 
for this one).</p><h3>Other notable fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Switching between read / write in editor no longer resets scroll position</li><li>The &quot;highlighted&quot; text color was changed from blue to yellow, to better separate highlight from selection</li><li>Added syntax highlighting support for Golang</li><li>Added support for floating images left and right</li><li>Added a toggle for starred status when viewing a document </li><li>Fixed &quot;ctrl-x&quot; key shortcuts not bound correctly in Windows browsers</li><li>Fixed search results not updating when changing filters without reloading</li><li>The &quot;New&quot; badge will no longer show to document creator</li><li>Google Drive embeds are now supported</li><li>And much more…</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>2020-in-review</guid>
    <title>2020 in Review</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/2020-in-review</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>2020 wasn’t without its challenges for many of us and I personally feel lucky to have gotten through the year with health and happiness intact. For Outline it was the biggest year ever for new features, fixes, and the growing community. Whether you’ve been following intently or this is the first time you’ve come across Outline here are some highlights from the past year:</p><h3>📝 A new editor</h3><p>We started the year with a new editor, completely rewritten from the ground up on the <a href="https://prosemirror.net">Prosemirror</a> framework. It’s now several orders of magnitude faster than the previous version at rendering both large and small documents, mobile compatible and a really solid base for the future. The editor is <a href="https://github.com/outline/rich-markdown-editor">open sourced</a> under a BSD license so you can play around with it in your projects too.</p><h3>⚡️ Performance</h3><p>I was already proud of Outline’s performance, and this year continued that focus. Special effort was put into dropping the initial download size of the entire application by more than 2Mb’s to ensure the app loads incredibly fast and documents load in milliseconds. </p><h3>🆕 New content types</h3><p>With the new editor came new functionality such as highlights, notice blocks, and rich embeds like Google Slides – plus a /slash menu for quickly performing actions with only the keyboard. A special focus was also put on linking with automatic backlinks, on-demand creation of new docs from within the editor, and <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.45.0">hover previews for internal links</a>. All this and still fully Markdown compatible.</p><p><img alt="New notice blocks" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/notice-panels.png"/></p><h3>👨‍👨‍👧‍👦 Permissions + access</h3><p>In March we made strides in improving the Outline experience for different kinds of teams with the addition of <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.41.0">groups</a>, group permissions, and read-only access to collections. Email sign-in for guests that aren’t part of your main organization and optional <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/custom-domains">custom domains</a> we’re also added.</p><p><img alt="Custom domains" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/custom-domains.png"/></p><h3>📄 Shared templates</h3><p>One of the hardest things with building a team knowledge base is keeping consistency of information. In August we introduced team templates that let you define <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/document-templates">shared templates</a> across the team that even include fillable “fields” to make starting new documents easy.</p><p><img alt="Shared templates" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/use-template.png"/></p><h3>🇺🇳 Translations</h3><p>One of the biggest advantages of having an open codebase is the contributions that are made from all around the world. It was always an aim to translate Outline and this year <a href="https://github.com/glaand">André</a> made that happen with implementation of the translation framework and process integrated with <a href="http://translate.getoutline.com/">CrowdIn</a></p><p>Outline is now translated into <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/spanish-french-korean">5 languages</a>, with more just around the corner.</p><h3>🌎 Social impact</h3><p>When I think about the places that Outline should direct its impact as a company, top of the list is in helping efforts that are tackling climate change. It’s easy to ensure that our own operations are carbon neutral as the footprint is so small – but this year we’ve also comped accounts to teams and communities working on climate change, and as of November 1% of all revenue is being donated to actively remove carbon from the atmosphere.</p><h3>The year ahead…</h3><p>For 2021 the roadmap is full and I’m excited to think about where the product will be by this time next year. Here’s a sneak peak of a couple of things that are “coming soon”… \n </p><ul><li>A continued focus on performance to ensure Outline remains the fastest knowledge base on the market.</li><li>“Bulk import” from other tools including Confluence and Notion</li><li>Realtime collaboration to allow multiple document editors at once</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>spanish-french-korean</guid>
    <title>Community Translations</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/spanish-french-korean</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>The last few weeks has seen a surge of support in the community for <a href="https://translate.getoutline.com">translating Outline</a>. We&#x27;re proud to now have initial support for the following languages in the product - head over to settings to choose your native language if you haven&#x27;t already.</p><ul><li>🇩🇪 German</li><li>🇪🇸 Spanish</li><li>🇫🇷 French</li><li>🇰🇷 Korean</li><li>🇵🇹 Portugese</li></ul><p>This week support for drag and drop to move documents in the sidebar also landed. Now that a solid technical foundation is in place reordering of documents is next on the list of improvements.</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Scrollbar styling on tables in documents is improved</li><li><code>CMD</code>+<code>Shift</code>+<code>P</code> shortcut now works to publish the document when the title is focused</li><li>Added <code>SQL</code> language support in code blocks</li><li>Fixed image captions not editable in Safari</li><li>Double click to edit a title in the sidebar now styled correctly in dark mode</li><li>Disabling public sharing at the team level now disables access to all previously shared links</li><li>Fixed an issue where some actions might not appear in document menu</li><li>Sidebar items no longer highlight when dragging incompatible items over them</li><li>Fixed potential server error when uploading images with particularly long file names</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>community-translation</guid>
    <title>👋 Hallo, 你好, こんにちは</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/community-translation</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline translations" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/translations.png"/></p><p>This week we&#x27;re really excited to kick-off a community translation project. Over the last month there has been a lot of work to hook up the framework and processes for accepting translations and it&#x27;s now finally ready to use. A special thanks
goes out to <a href="https://github.com/glaand">André Glatzl</a> for pushing this forward.</p><p>If you&#x27;d like to see Outline translated into your native language and can offer a little time to help out, it&#x27;s easy to contribute – simply head to <a href="https://translate.getoutline.com">translate.getoutline.com</a> and sign up for a free CrowdIn account. Accepted translations are automatically merged back into the codebase and will be available in the following release.</p><p>Right now German and Portugese are already &gt;30% complete and we&#x27;re looking for some folks to take the lead on Chinese, Japanese, and Spanish in particular.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>custom-domains</guid>
    <title>Custom domains</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/custom-domains</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline custom domain" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/custom-domains.png"/></p><p>This week brings support for custom domains to the cloud hosted version of Outline.
Now you can easily have <code>wiki.myteam.com</code> or <code>kb.yourcompany.com</code> without the
hassle of hosting your own Outline servers.</p><p>Custom domains are available as an add-on for a flat rate of <strong>$20/mo</strong>. Interested? <a href="/contact">Contact support</a> to arrange setup for your team.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>confluence-import</guid>
    <title>Import from Confluence</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/confluence-import</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>We&#x27;ve made further improvements to importing, in particular it&#x27;s now possible to import <code>.doc</code> files that are exported from Confluence, this is now the recommended format to get content from Confluence into Outline as it supports the greatest range of formatting – including tables.</p><p>We plan on releasing a CLI tool soon to allow bulk import for Confluence, Notion, GitHub and other services – watch this space!</p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><h4>Platform</h4><ul><li>Teams using Google Workspace to sign-in can now still search their wiki from Slack after connecting in settings (previously this required Slack auth).</li><li>Notification emails are now a little delayed to reduce the chances of receiving too many.</li><li>Realtime connections are now more performant in Safari, aka the websocket doesn&#x27;t always fall back to long-polling!</li></ul><h4>Editor</h4><ul><li>When scrolling to headers from the table of contents the document will no longer scroll behind the fixed header area.</li><li>There is no longer an erroneous pointer cursor on headings.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>something-brewing</guid>
    <title>We&#039;ve got something brewing…</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/something-brewing</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Brewing" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/multiplayer.png"/></p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Spotify embeds have been improved and better handle the wide variety of possible link types</li><li>Fixed an issue that made it impossible to upload the same image twice without reloading the document</li><li>Improved toolbar behavior to prevent it appearing with an empty selection</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>import-from-word</guid>
    <title>Import from Microsoft Word</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/import-from-word</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Much like last months update our focus continues to be on little details, performance, and bug fixing rather than new features – but some solid new functionality did sneak in with the help of open source contributors…</p><h3>HTML + Word Import</h3><p>You can now import HTML and Microsoft Word documents simply by dragging them onto a collection, or from the collection context menu. We also improved the look and feel of GSuite embeds.</p><h3>New + Unread badges</h3><p>Lists of documents now show when you last viewed the doc – and new, unread documents are highlighted with a badge so it&#x27;s easier to spot changes you missed.</p><p><img alt="new document badge" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/new-badge.png"/></p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><h4>Platform</h4><ul><li>Share links can now be embedded in iframes</li><li>Document and collection titles can now be edited from the sidebar by double clicking</li><li>Improvements to focus accessibility</li><li>You can now unpublish a document that was previously published via the overflow &quot;...&quot; menu</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to restore documents when their collection has been deleted</li><li>When a document is deleted the metadata now reflects the correct user</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to view all possible locations when choosing where to move a document</li><li>An issue with nested modals not stacking correctly</li><li>Clicking to &quot;change permissions&quot; when editing a collection now works correctly</li><li>A document that previously had it&#x27;s share revoked can now be re-shared</li><li>Shares related to deleted documents no longer appear in the admin area</li><li>It&#x27;s no longer possible to create a child document inside a deleted document</li><li>Improved handling of deleted documents/collections over websockets</li><li>Fixed new revisions being skipped if identical to previously autosaved revision</li><li>Document history sidebar now has a header and button to close</li></ul><h4>Editor</h4><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to use line breaks in table cells with <code>Shift</code>+<code>Enter</code> </li><li>Google docs, sheets and presentations can now be embedded without requiring &quot;Publish to web&quot; first</li><li>Styling and behavior of doc link search was improved to be more reliable</li><li>Selected content in the editor can now be dragged to reorder</li><li>Table of contents now shows correctly when navigating directly to a document url (eg from a bookmark)</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to toggle a blockquote via the formatting toolbar (previously blockquotes would be continuously nested)</li><li>Headers inside notice blocks are now the correct color in dark mode</li><li>Checkboxes can now be toggled in read only mode via the keyboard</li><li>Enter key in document title now adds a new paragraph below the title</li><li>Keyboard shortcuts now work when document title is focused</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to underline text in the editor with <code>CMD+U</code></li><li>Horizontal dividers are no longer selectable in read-only</li><li>Automatic linking of pasted URL&#x27;s is now more reliable</li><li>Document titles no longer look faded in Safari</li><li>Fixed cursor navigation around headings in Firefox</li><li>There is no longer a small pointer dead zone over links when hover card is visible</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to select embeds in the editor</li><li>&quot;ClickUp&quot; added to embed integrations</li><li>The positioning of the formatting toolbar has been improved to be more predictable</li><li>It is now possible to search for existing docs using their URL</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>the-one-with-all-the-fixes</guid>
    <title>The one with all the fixes</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/the-one-with-all-the-fixes</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>The last two weeks we&#x27;ve been focused on bug fixing, performance and reliability. We&#x27;ve always taken pride in the speed of Outline and keeping the app fast requires constant ongoing attention and maintenance. One place that hadn&#x27;t been optimized in a while was the initial javascript bundle download size, which has now dropped from <code>2.8Mb</code> to just <code>700Kb</code>.</p><p>Some of this updates improvements (Marked with a <!-- -->[<!-- -->os<!-- -->]<!-- -->) are brought to you by open source contributions, for this we&#x27;re very thankful!</p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>[<!-- -->os<!-- -->]<!-- --> It&#x27;s now (finally) possible to use line breaks in table cells with <code>Shift</code>+<code>Enter</code></li><li>[<!-- -->os<!-- -->]<!-- --> The document history sidebar now has a header and a button to close</li><li>The interface for moving documents got cleaned up and it&#x27;s now easier to tell where the moved document will end up</li><li>The app will now redirect to the parent document instead of the collection when deleting a child document</li><li>[<!-- -->os<!-- -->]<!-- --> You can now unpublish a document that was previously published via the overflow (<code>...</code>) document menu</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Selected content in the editor can now be dragged to reorder</li><li>When a document is deleted the metadata now reflects the correct user</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to view all possible locations when choosing where to move a document</li><li>Table of contents now shows correctly when navigating directly to a document</li><li>A document that previously had it&#x27;s share revoked can now be reshared if you have permission</li><li>Shares related to deleted documents no longer appear in the admin listing</li><li>The option to create a child document inside a document in the trash no longer appears</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to toggle a blockquote via the formatting toolbar (previously blockquotes would be continuously nested)</li><li>Headers inside notice blocks are now the correct color in dark mode</li><li>Checkboxes toggled via the keyboard are now persisted correctly</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>document-templates</guid>
    <title>Document templates are here</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/document-templates</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p>Today we’re adding the much-requested ability to create team document templates in Outline.
Templates are a simple, but powerful way to keep your docs consistent and reliable. In 
the near future we’ll also publish recommended templates and make them easy to use from 
within your team.</p><h3>How to create a template</h3><p>There are two ways to create a template:</p><ol><li>Navigate to &quot;Templates&quot; in the left sidebar, then hit &quot;New template…&quot; in the top right, 
choose a collection and write your template.</li><li>Find an existing doc that you would like to create a template from, click on the overflow menu &quot;...&quot; (usually in the top right) and then &quot;Create template…&quot;.</li></ol><p><img alt="Outline create template" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/create-template.png"/></p><p>Once you’re editing a template, simply highlight some text and click on the new &quot;placeholder&quot; icon in the toolbar to convert the text into a placeholder that can be filled out by anyone that creates a new doc from the template.</p><h3>How to use a template</h3><p>Simply start a new doc, a &quot;Templates&quot; option will appear in the top right corner until the 
document is first saved.</p><p><img alt="Outline use a template" src="/images/use-template.png"/></p><h3>Other fixes and improvements</h3><ul><li>Click on the last updated timestamp below the document title now opens the history sidebar.</li><li>The behavior of the floating toolbar was improved.</li><li>It is now possible to toggle the state of checkboxes without explicitly going into &quot;Edit&quot;.</li><li>When a document is publicly shared this is now denoted by a globe icon in the share button.</li><li>Fixed some ugly styling issues introduced by the latest Chrome releases.</li><li>Fixed an issue where after you have chosen a collection icon it might get reset if you continue to edit the collection name.</li><li>Fixed a case where websocket connections would not reconnect automatically.</li><li>Fixed an issue that would prevent editing the beginning of long collection descriptions.</li><li>Fixed rendering of GitHub Gist embeds.</li><li>Fixed an error that could on rare occasions cause the app to form a reload loop.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>notice-panels</guid>
    <title>New notice panels</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/notice-panels</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><img alt="Outline notice panels" src="https://www.getoutline.com/images/notice-panels.png"/></p><p>This week we added a new content type for your documents called &quot;notices&quot;. You
can use them to highlight information for readers such as important information, or to add additional context around the main content.</p><p>There are three types of notices available today – &quot;info&quot;, &quot;warning&quot;, and &quot;tip&quot;.</p><h3>How to use</h3><p>As always, you can access blocks through the /slash menu, just type <code>/notice</code> on a new line, <code>/tip</code>, <code>/warning</code> and many others will work too so you don’t need to remember specific incantations… It’s also possible to type <code>:::</code> as a shortcut to insert a new notice in a hurry.</p><h3>Other improvements</h3><ul><li>When creating a new collection an icon is no longer automatically chosen once you’ve picked one manually. </li><li>We made some improvements to last releases &quot;hover previews&quot; so that more information is visible.</li><li>There is now a link to create an account from the sign-in page.</li><li>Several styling, layout, and focus issues were tidied up.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.45.0</guid>
    <title>v0.45.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.45.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Hovering over internal links to other documents now shows detailed &quot;preview cards&quot; so you can get an idea of the document without clicking through. </li></ul><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/87752925-5149fc80-c7b6-11ea-9c71-04964a3375e1.png"/></p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>A new, cleaner and faster login page</li><li>The team name is now shown in page titles</li><li>A new <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/developers#tag/Documents/paths/~1documents.export/post">documents.export endpoint</a> was added to the API to quickly grab documents in Markdown format</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Lucidchart embeds now work across the various Lucidchart subdomains</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 18:53:30 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.44.0</guid>
    <title>v0.44.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.44.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>The slash menu now has the option to create a link</li><li>You can now make collections easier to discover and pick out in the sidebar by setting an icon and color.</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Various mistakes in API documentation have been addressed</li><li>Editor placeholder is now hidden when uploading an image</li><li>Document meta data, references, and editor UI are no longer visible when printing a document</li><li>Italics and blockquotes are now displayed correctly when printing in Google Chrome</li><li>Email signin users are now marked as active when they first accept an invite</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 20:11:22 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.43.3</guid>
    <title>v0.43.3</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.43.3</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to create documents directly from the link editor, or hit <code>CMD+K</code> and type a document title</li><li>Improved loading state for the sidebar</li><li>Improved readability of some UI in dark mode</li><li>Documents will now update in realtime when reading and another user edits</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s no longer possible to trigger the keyboard shortcut help by typing &quot;?&quot; when editing a document</li><li>Admins can now downgrade a suspended admin to a user</li><li>User profile now reads &#x27;invited&#x27; instead of &#x27;joined&#x27; when team member has yet to sign-in</li><li>Backslash in search queries is now correctly escaped</li><li>Suspended users no longer show as options when adding team members to groups and collections</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 18:46:15 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.43.2</guid>
    <title>v0.43.2</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.43.2</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Exported markdown files are now cleaner than ever before</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an issue that could cause checkbox list items with escaped characters in the text to show the escape characters after reload</li><li>Fixed an error when adding Github Gist embeds</li><li>Fixed an error when attempting to load a group where a user has had their account removed</li><li>Invalid regex error on Safari when filtering users with some characters</li><li>We now auto focus the search input when adding users to a collection</li><li>Imported documents now get a best-guess title based on the content and file name</li><li>It&#x27;s no longer possible to get checkbox state out of sync with view by clicking rapidly</li><li>Placeholder or &quot;Type / to insert text&quot; can no longer can appear behind images</li><li>Fixed an error when pasting markdown into the document</li><li>Fixed an error when attempting to make a selection that surrounds an embed</li><li>Pressing &quot;Escape&quot; key in link editor now restores editor focus</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 15:41:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.43.1</guid>
    <title>v0.43.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.43.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Code blocks imported from other sources with unsupported languages no longer crash the editor</li><li>Overlay background when zooming into images now respects the theme</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 05:24:04 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.43.0</guid>
    <title>v0.43.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.43.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>This is the biggest release of Outline since we first published the source code. The <a href="https://github.com/outline/rich-markdown-editor">editor</a> is entirely rebuilt from the ground up for extensibility and speed, allowing us to move faster than ever before and is the culmination of more than 4 months of planning and work.</p><p>The improvements and fixes are almost too numerous to count, but the most important are listed below:</p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Document rendering performance increased by leaps and bounds, some of our extreme test documents went from 30seconds -&gt; 300ms to render</li><li>A new menu for inserting blocks is much more intuitive than before, type &quot;/&quot; at the beginning of a line or hit the &quot;+&quot; button to trigger</li></ul><p><img alt="Outline block menu" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/82714444-676a8f00-9c43-11ea-99f3-c89b6536c10b.gif"/></p><ul><li>Updating a document&#x27;s title now also updates any links to the document in other docs automatically</li><li>&quot;Highlight&quot; now appears as an option in the formatting menu</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to type a url in markdown formatting</li><li>Quotes are converted to smart quotes as you type</li><li>Support for paragraph breaks in list items</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to choose the &quot;system&quot; theme and have Outline follow your system&#x27;s dark mode preference – this is especially useful on macOS when dark mode is set to &quot;auto&quot; to go dark in the evenings.</li></ul><p><img alt="Outline appearance preference" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/82713920-8a943f00-9c41-11ea-9f32-ce381b90f1c3.png"/></p><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Support for alternative input methods, this finally brings the fix for typing in Chinese, Korean, Japanese, and all other languages that use a soft keyboard for input.</li><li>Restored the ability to disable embeds on a single doc in the context menu</li><li>Fixed some extra scrollbars that appear depending on your input device</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to save a document with only a title</li><li>Long titles now wrap onto multiple lines again</li><li>Document headings are centered correctly again when scrolled</li><li>Adding a new row to a table now respects column alignment</li><li>Improved key handling in link editor</li><li>Issues with markdown shortcuts surrounded in whitespace not applying</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 22:20:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.42.2</guid>
    <title>v0.42.2</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.42.2</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Buttons now stand out better in dark mode</li><li>If the editor fails to load because a deploy happened the app will now auto-recover</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed a regression in the styling of document titles in dark mode</li><li>Improved the usability of the image cropping tool in dark mode</li><li>Escape characters no longer incorrectly appear in the table of contents</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 17:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.42.1</guid>
    <title>v0.42.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.42.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Crash on share links introduced in previous release</li><li>Crash on editing documents with image/embed as first node</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 05:50:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.42.0</guid>
    <title>v0.42.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.42.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li><p>The table of contents moved from being hidden on the edge of the screen to optionally toggleable inline with the document content. It follows your scroll position, highlights the active section and is just generally much more usable now. Toggle on the new contents with the icon at the end of the breadcrumb in the document header.</p></li><li><p>Titles also gained a metadata line underneath which shows the last team member to edit the document and the total number of times it&#x27;s been viewed – we plan to keep increasing the utility of this area.</p></li></ul><p><img alt="screenshot" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/78515483-ec204d00-776a-11ea-8c01-908848af58eb.png"/></p><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Timestamps now update while you&#x27;re viewing a screen without needing to navigate or refresh.</li><li>The document history sidebar now scrolls independently of the document content</li><li>The document history sidebar now loads correctly if you navigate straight to a history link</li><li>Document updated notification emails now take into account your teams subdomain</li><li>All collaborators on a document will now receive notification emails, rather than just the document creator (If they have chosen to do so in settings).</li><li><code>&lt; Back</code> buttons in modals can no longer scroll off-screen</li><li>Long document titles are now better handled in the navigation sidebar</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 01:27:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.41.0</guid>
    <title>v0.41.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.41.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><p>Groups! It&#x27;s now possible to organize your team into groups and assign groups with read or write permissions to collections. You can use this to give part of your team read-only access and retain write access for others.</p><p>You can manage groups from <strong>Settings -&gt; Groups</strong> or directly from any <strong>Collection -&gt; Permissions…</strong></p><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/76828453-33f02c00-67de-11ea-8a41-4cc7eef6e34e.png"/></p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Embeds are now supported for Google Docs, Slides, and Sheets</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed a link in the welcome documents to point to the public site.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 06:18:41 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.40.2</guid>
    <title>v0.40.2</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.40.2</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Newly created documents should auto focus</li><li>Clicking in whitespace at end of document should focus on the last line</li><li>Alignment of document loading placeholder</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 06:36:07 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.40.1</guid>
    <title>v0.40.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.40.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>The people management screens now include pagination to support larger teams</li><li>When a modal opens from a modal it now visually &quot;stacks&quot; to provide a navigational clue</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Rich embeds are now enabled on publicly shared documents</li><li>Fixed an issue where newly created private collections would be missing some available actions until the app is reloaded</li><li>The &quot;New nested document&quot; option no longer appears for drafts (previously it errored)</li><li>Attempt to edit a document while viewing it&#x27;s history no longer errors</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 05:14:31 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.40.0</guid>
    <title>v0.40.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.40.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>We&#x27;re continuing to make great headway with two big features in February; rewriting the editor to be more stable and performant (think 10x faster!) and bringing group permissions to the app. In the meantime, some important fixes have also been made in the last few weeks…</p><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to access documents with _ or ~ characters in the title, previously links would break</li><li>Also, it was possible for navigation to get &#x27;stuck&#x27; when moving between documents with similar titles, this no longer happens</li><li>Slack notifications are now working correctly again</li><li>The app will no longer break if a deploy happens between loading the app and loading a document (quite the edge case!)</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 04:44:55 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.39.0</guid>
    <title>v0.39.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.39.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Other team members presence is now shown on documents – you can see when others are viewing or editing!</li><li>We added easily accessible search inputs at the top of the &quot;Home&quot; page and collection screens</li><li>Your own drafts are now visible in collections instead of having to go specifically to the &quot;Drafts&quot; section </li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Documents returned in search results no longer have an empty context menu</li><li>Invited users no longer appear as an option in &quot;Filter by author&quot;</li><li>Search filter dropdowns no longer have unnecessary scrollbars</li><li>The sidebar in dark mode on mobile is no longer partially transparent</li><li>Creating and revoking API keys now produces events in the audit trail</li><li>Drafts no longer appear as options to insert as links into documents</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 03:37:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.38.1</guid>
    <title>v0.38.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.38.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Documents with nested sub-documents now display an index view more prominently</li><li>Clicking into a document will preload it&#x27;s nested documents for faster navigation</li><li>In the API <code>parentDocumentId</code> is now available as a filter for listing documents</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>The &quot;Invite people&quot; view did not work when accessed from &quot;Collection members&quot;, it now works as expected</li><li>Emails are now stored and processed only in lowercase</li><li>Sidebar did not display correctly on mobile when editing a document</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 04:20:43 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.38.0</guid>
    <title>v0.38.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.38.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to invite guests to your wiki that can sign-in with their email address.</li><li>We added the &quot;Trash&quot; menu item in the sidebar which shows recently deleted documents and gives you an opportunity to restore them for 30 days.</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added a new keyboard shortcut (<code>CMD+SHIFT+P</code>) to publish the current document </li><li>Added support for InVision live image links</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Selecting &quot;Document history&quot; when the history sidebar is already open now closes the sidebar</li><li>Toggling &quot;Starred&quot; in the document menu now keeps the menu open so that feedback is visible</li><li>Fixed an issue that would prevent moving a document inside another within a private collection</li><li>&quot;Import document&quot; in collection menu now works when triggered from the sidebar</li><li>Fixed an issue that caused regex-like search queries to error</li><li>Fixed unable to embolden hashtags in editor</li><li>Fixed an extra space character in the editor when typing markdown shortcuts</li><li>Fixed a display issues with collaborator avatars not overlapping</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 07:21:41 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.37.0</guid>
    <title>v0.37.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.37.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>It is now possible to set a collection membership to be <code>read-only</code>, this is currently only an option in private collections but will soon be extended to all collections.</li><li>&quot;Child documents&quot; are now automatically listed at the bottom of a document</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>The people list now shows the time the person was last active instead of when they joined the team.</li><li>Added a button to create a new document when no search results are returned for a query</li><li>Drafts now have a clear badge and show which collection the draft is published in</li><li>Improved the behavior of sidebar collapsing and nesting</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Attempting to sign-in to a suspended account now shows a useful message</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to use the Slack integration in conjunction with Google sign-in</li><li>Popover menus can no longer open off-screen</li><li>The first auto-save of a document no longer causes the text cursor to become unfocused</li><li>Fixed an issue where the audit log would fail to log if any of the event actors had been deleted</li><li>Importing documents using drag-n-drop no longer causes it to potentially appear under multiple sub-documents</li><li>Attempting to export an empty collection no longer fails</li><li>Removed an orphaned header when there are no archived documents</li><li>Duplicating a draft no longer automatically publishes the duplicate</li><li>Document no longer appears blank if you create a link back to itself</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 04:10:22 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.36.1</guid>
    <title>v0.36.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.36.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Document title size</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 04:19:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.36.0</guid>
    <title>v0.36.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.36.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Documents in private collections now show a little padlock next to the collection name in feeds such as Home, Starred, and Drafts.</li><li>The color picker for collections got an upgrade it&#x27;s now a little less <strong>in your face</strong> when creating a new collection</li><li>Tooltips now show applicable keyboard shortcuts to make it easier to learn!</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Improved accessibility of buttons, added new focus states</li><li>Visiting a doc without permission will now display a &quot;Not found&quot; screen rather than forever loading</li><li>Added missing display of audit log events for user promotion / demotion and suspension</li><li>Fixed some heading alignments</li><li>Improved client side security by adding extensive CSP rules to all html responses</li><li>Slack notifications are now sent on the publish event again</li><li>Infinite loading document lists no longer jump back to the top while scrolling</li><li>Restored selected state for images and horizontal rules</li><li>Headings in the editor now start at level 2 to take into account level 1 title</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 22:42:23 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.35.0</guid>
    <title>v0.35.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.35.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added <a href="http://www.opensearch.org/Home">Open Search</a> support</li><li>The document menu now includes an &quot;Edit&quot; option</li><li>Added a new way to access the keyboard shortcut reference from the bottom right corner of documents</li><li>The API now allows exporting your knowledge base as a zip file directly (<a href="https://www.getoutline.com/developers">reference</a>)</li><li>Links added in the editor now have a protocol added automatically if missing</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Minor button alignment and padding issues </li><li>Toolbar no longer shows unavailable options when selecting text in a heading</li><li>Attempting to create a link in a heading no longer causes text to disappear</li><li>Empty headings are no longer misformatted on reload</li><li>Speed of rendering tables was greatly improved</li><li>Loading more data than necessary on first open</li><li>Embeds did not show highlight outline when selected</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 03:26:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.34.0</guid>
    <title>v0.34.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.34.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Audit log. Actions taken by team members in your wiki are now recorded in an audit log accessible to admins.</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Exporting a collection now downloads a zip file instantly, rather than emailing</li><li>Added support for additional Mindmeister link formats</li><li>Updated branding of RealtimeBoard to Miro</li><li>Visiting a route / document while signed out will now attempt to redirect back after signing in</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Duplicate document menu option works again</li><li>API requests to unknown endpoints no longer echo back request</li><li>No longer possible to double wrap links</li><li>The link toolbar now always saves edits on blur / exit</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 06:23:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.33.0</guid>
    <title>v0.33.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.33.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><p>This release includes references (or <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Backlink">backlinks</a>) – these are automated links that are shown at the bottom of a document telling you which other documents it was linked from. Backlinks have been a feature of wiki software for many years and it&#x27;s great to have first class support in Outline.</p><p><img alt="Backlinks in Outline" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/61175979-3aeade80-a56d-11e9-9341-c19efc10bc35.png"/></p><p>To create a reference you only need to link to another document in your knowledgebase.</p><blockquote><p><em>Hint:</em> Select some text and hit the <code>CMD+K</code> shortcut to quickly create a link.</p></blockquote><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>The &quot;...&quot; document menu is now available from the sidebar</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to create public share links to your drafts</li><li>Clearer buttons and &quot;New doc&quot; actions</li><li>Improved the first-run onboarding documents to be more helpful and descriptive</li><li>Improved color accessibility</li><li>Tightened up list and link styling</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed a UI performance regression introduced by tooltips</li><li>Fixed an issue that would cause Save/Publish buttons to show as disabled for an extended amount of time when creating a new document</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 19:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.32.0</guid>
    <title>v0.32.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.32.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>We&#x27;ve added the ability to send team members invites directly from within the app</li></ul><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/60153280-a6286880-9798-11e9-8ee6-9c4fed06183a.png"/></p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Notification settings now displays your account email address</li><li>Updating your email address in Slack/Google will now update in Outline automatically on next sign-in</li><li>The Slack slash command now responds to <code>/outline help</code> with some useful instructions</li><li>Deeply nested documents now display a vertical breadcrumb in the header</li><li>Improved accessibility of content in modals</li><li>Editor buttons now have descriptive tooltips</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>The Slack slash command no longer errors if you provide no search term</li><li>Deleting a collection locally or remotely now does a better job of cleaning up data</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to use markdown shortcuts inside table cells</li><li>Collapsing headings now respects the heading level correctly</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 04:48:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.31.0</guid>
    <title>v0.31.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.31.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to disable highlighting in code blocks to just display plain, pre-formatted text</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Users in search filters are now correctly ordered</li><li>Self hosted installations now support AWS S3 signature version 4</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 07:36:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.30.0</guid>
    <title>v0.30.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.30.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><p>This release brings support for creating and editing simple Tables in all your documents. </p><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/58373984-081c5680-7eeb-11e9-8605-5159812f7b55.png"/></p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added optional <code>append</code> flag to <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/developers">documents.update</a> API endpoint to allow appending content to the end of a document</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Block Insert no longer appears on top of formatting toolbar</li><li>Blockquote can now be toggled from the formatting toolbar</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 06:40:49 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.29.0</guid>
    <title>v0.29.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.29.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added support for embedding <a href="https://abstract.com/blog/public-sharing/">Abstract public share links</a></li><li>Added <code>Bash</code> and <code>Powershell</code> formatting options in code blocks</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed editor scroll jumping when focusing the bottom of large documents</li><li>Fixed stars and underscores disappearing in code blocks on save</li><li>Updated the <a href="https://www.loom.com">loom</a> integration to work with their fancy new loom.com domain name</li><li>Dropdown filters on the search page now close on click</li><li>Fixed some more potential edge-case errors in the editor</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 02:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.28.0</guid>
    <title>v0.28.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.28.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Outline now utilizes websockets to keep everything in sync without refreshing the tab</li><li>New <strong>filtering options</strong> when searching. Refine results by collection, author, or date to get to the information you&#x27;re looking for faster!</li></ul><p><img alt="Outline wiki search filters" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/56595692-f0784800-65a3-11e9-96d0-d712e1468538.png"/></p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>This changelog now has an RSS feed if that&#x27;s your kind of thing</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>The <code>M</code> key is correctly mapped to &quot;Move document&quot; again</li><li>The <code>ESC</code> key no longer reverts to editing mode after exiting it</li><li>Creating a horizontal divider after a paragraph without a space would be interpreted as a heading after reload</li><li>Restored missing divider on document header</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 14:59:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.27.0</guid>
    <title>v0.27.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.27.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>The full path to nested documents is now shown in search results</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to move documents between collections and to any level of nesting</li><li>Added the ability to optionally include archived documents in search results</li><li>Improved editor performance and memory usage</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed <code>Tab</code> key should allow nesting of lists</li><li>Fixed a crash in the editor when deleting links</li><li>Fixed able to open the move document dialog from a draft</li><li>Fixed sub heading beginning with same emoji as title becomes incorrectly inset</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 04:28:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.26.0</guid>
    <title>v0.26.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.26.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Document archive, you can now choose to store documents outside of a collection without deleting them.</li><li>A little thing called <strong>night mode</strong>! Toggle in the settings menu whether you prefer Outline to be daylight white 🌞 or midnight black 🌚.</li></ul><p><img alt="night mode" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/54256676-095bfb00-451a-11e9-8120-1eb9f87138fa.png"/></p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li><code>CMD+Enter</code> will now publish the current document if it&#x27;s a draft</li><li>The <code>Esc</code> key now exits editing a document</li><li>The <code>N</code> key is now a shortcut to start a new document in the current collection</li><li>Improved the empty state for user profiles</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed list editing functionality in editor</li><li>Fixed a bug that could result in a corrupted session cookie when signing out of one account while signed in to multiple accounts</li><li>Updated to Slack&#x27;s fancy new icon</li><li>When sharing a link to a heading the page will now scroll to the heading correctly once the document loads</li><li>Fixed adding Outline as a PWA now works correctly</li><li>Fixed keyboard shortcuts now display correctly to non-mac users</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 23:23:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.25.0</guid>
    <title>v0.25.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.25.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added support for <a href="https://www.mindmeister.com">Mindmeister</a> embeds</li><li>When searching from Slack a &quot;Post to Channel&quot; option is now available so you can share the best search results with your team directly</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Lines inside code blocks are no longer individually scrollable</li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to link to places on the same subdomain that aren&#x27;t in the wiki</li><li>Insertion marks (++) no longer disappear on save</li><li>Suspended users now see the correct error message when attempting to sign in</li><li>The collections sidebar no longer scrolls to the top when changing documents</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 04:26:17 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.24.0</guid>
    <title>v0.24.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.24.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Headings can now be collapsed</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Updated Slack branding</li><li>Keyboard behavior when editing block quotes has been improved</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Lines in code blocks can now be easily deleted</li><li>Code block horizontal scroll behavior has been fixed</li><li>Image captions now wrap to multiple lines</li><li>Multiline block quotes no longer collapse onto a single line on save</li><li>Fixed link in welcome email did not include team subdomain</li><li>Tables in imported documents are no longer removed on save</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 09:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.23.0</guid>
    <title>v0.23.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.23.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Added user profiles! Click on any avatar to see a brief profile of the user and the documents they&#x27;ve been editing.</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Improved Editor and UI performance</li><li>Improved tooltips on collaborators and viewers to be much clearer</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed a number of small Editor bugs</li><li>An issue where triggering multiple toast messages in quick succession would leave some hanging in the UI</li><li>Slack notifications for edited documents now correctly display the author of the update, rather than the original creator of the document</li><li>RealtimeBoard and Vimeo embeds now correctly embed the secure version</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 02:20:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.22.0</guid>
    <title>v0.22.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.22.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Added the ability to see which team members have viewed a document, and when</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added new sort options to collections including &quot;Least recently updated&quot; and alphabetical</li><li>Search now includes partial word matching</li><li>Search now has a local cache to increase the speed – navigating back from a document to search results is now instant.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 06:16:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.21.0</guid>
    <title>v0.21.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.21.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>Welcome to the first release of 2019! We&#x27;re kicking the year off right with a big new feature – private collections. It&#x27;s now possible to create a hidden collection that is only visible to team members that you invite, a much requested addition.</p><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Private collections</li><li>Google Slides embed support</li><li>Prezi embed support</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Improved the clarity and simplicity of the navigation sidebar</li><li>Improved button styling throughout</li><li>Added a dismissible help tip on the dashboard to help onboarding new teams</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed typeface fallback for non-latin languages</li><li>Lucidchart embeds fixed</li><li>Broken links in Slack notifications when team has custom subdomain</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 01:19:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.20.0</guid>
    <title>v0.20.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.20.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>The public content pages got a bit of a facelift, we made the API reference easier to browse, added a sidebar in this here changelog and added pages for all of the <a href="https://www.getoutline.com/integrations">integrations that Outline supports</a>.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 06:35:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.19.1</guid>
    <title>v0.19.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.19.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Errors when authenticating Slack commands from a team subdomain</li><li>The block toolbar now hides automatically when clicking to focus the document</li><li>The block insert menu no longer appears when hovering an embed</li><li>A message is now displayed when copying a link to a heading in a shared document</li><li>&quot;Your Teams&quot; menu item no longer erroneously shows up on content pages when logged into a single non-subdomain team.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 08:42:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.19.0</guid>
    <title>v0.19.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.19.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li><p>This release introduces <strong>rich document embeds</strong>. Pasting share links from supported services will now show an interactive embed inside the document. The following services are support at this time:</p><ul><li><a href="https://github.com">GitHub</a></li><li><a href="https://numceracy.co">Numeracy</a></li><li><a href="https://modeanalytics.com">Mode Analytics</a></li><li><a href="https://figma.com">Figma</a></li><li><a href="https://airtable.com">Airtable</a></li><li><a href="https://vimeo.com">Vimeo</a></li><li><a href="https://miro.com">Miro</a></li><li><a href="https://useloom.com">Loom</a></li><li><a href="https://lucidcharts.com">Lucidcharts</a></li><li><a href="https://framer.com">Framer</a></li><li><a href="https://invision.com">InVision</a></li><li><a href="https://typeform.com">Typeform</a></li><li><a href="https://marvelapp.com">Marvel</a></li><li><a href="https://spotify.com">Spotify</a></li><li><a href="https://codepen.io">Codepen</a></li><li><a href="https://trello.com">Trello</a></li></ul></li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Collections not visible in settings after connecting Slack</li><li>Teams with non-latin characters in their names unable to signin</li><li>Several issues with the recent document notifications addition</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 22:45:03 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.18.0</guid>
    <title>v0.18.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.18.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Secure subdomains are now available for your team! Head to the <a href="https://app.getoutline.com/settings/details">team settings</a> to choose or update your subdomain. Once a subdomain is set new logins will automatically be redirected.</li></ul><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/49562798-e3e3a380-f8d1-11e8-9bca-e596b60b72f9.png"/></p><ul><li>We added optional notifications for documents published, documents edited, and collections created. Choose your own <a href="https://app.getoutline.com/settings/notifications">notification settings</a> here.</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an issue that would cause the server to hang on requests to load document revisions</li><li>Fixed collection delete option appearing visible to non admins</li><li>Improved error messaging when offline</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 05:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.16.3</guid>
    <title>v0.16.3</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.16.3</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>It is now possible to choose the language for highlighting in code blocks 🙌</li></ul><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/48926979-56db2c00-ee87-11e8-8dbf-a92349df6b3c.png"/></p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>We added some subtle branding to shared documents</li><li>Recently viewed and edited documents are now displayed in a more sensible order</li><li>The name of the documents collection is now visible on the &quot;Starred&quot; screen</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fully deleting an image in the editor no longer requires hitting backspace twice</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 03:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.17.0</guid>
    <title>v0.17.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.17.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><p>We added a rich text area to the top of collections so you can add more details than just a name. This is great for when a collection represents an area of your company and makes it easy to add links to other company resources.</p><hr/><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/48729101-9b4a9b80-ebeb-11e8-919c-f12144012351.png"/></p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 19:07:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.16.2</guid>
    <title>v0.16.2</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.16.2</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added filtering options to the admin &quot;People&quot; listing</li><li>Profile picture is now saved once uploaded</li><li>Optimized images</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an issue where dashes within a hashtag would be escaped on save</li><li>Google Analytics events are now triggered correctly for more than the first page load</li><li>Fixed some UI jank when resizing a large uploaded profile picture</li><li>Fixed a layout issue on keyboard shortcuts dialog on Linux</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 04:26:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.16.1</guid>
    <title>v0.16.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.16.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Document history menu can now be opened again</li><li>It is now possible to underline text in the editor and have that persist</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Upgraded dependencies for improved performance</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 06:42:03 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.16.0</guid>
    <title>v0.16.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.16.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Upgrades the editor</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an issue with S3 uploads for self hosted configuration</li><li>Fixed issue when title of a document includes the word &quot;history&quot;</li><li>SSL is now enforced on subdomains</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 19:48:35 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.15.1</guid>
    <title>v0.15.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.15.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Visual feedback when avatars and logos are uploading</li><li>Fixed a couple of server side issues when deleting documents</li><li>Added Zapier to integrations</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 16:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.15.0</guid>
    <title>v0.15.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.15.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>It is now possible to see a documents version history from the &quot;...&quot; menu select &quot;Document history&quot;. You can also restore a previous version, creating a new one if you need to easily go back to how things were.</li></ul><p><img alt="image" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/46253740-0c65a200-c438-11e8-84b3-760f87fac1cd.png"/></p><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Restored the collection name on documents listed on the dashboard</li><li>Fixed an issue where document content changed between image uploading start and finish is lost</li><li>Fixes an issue where an image is lost after upload if document is immediately closed without further edits</li><li>Fixed an issue that could cause <code>undefined</code> to appear in the document</li><li>Fixed an editor issue that would result in an extra newline before links that wrap <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/778">#778</a></li><li>Fixed typos in the welcome email and document 🙈</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 05:36:11 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.14.0</guid>
    <title>v0.14.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.14.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>We&#x27;ve been working on a <a href="https://zapier.com">Zapier</a> integration. If you&#x27;re interested in hooking Outline events up to other aspects of your teams workflow, give it a look! React to documents being created or automatically create documents in specific collections from external events. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline-zapier">Find more information on the Zapier integation here</a>.</p><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>The dashboard now features three tabs &quot;Recently viewed&quot;, &quot;Recently updated&quot;, and &quot;Created by me&quot; to allow easier discovery. We also added infinite pagination to these dashboard tabs</li><li>This release adds the ability to restrict public sharing of documents, check out the new <a href="https://app.getoutline.com/settings/security">security section</a> in your Outline settings</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Improved performance of the editor when typing in large documents</li><li>Creating a new document now shows a menu to clarify and choose exactly where the document will go</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>The block toolbar items were incorrectly colored, making them difficult to see</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 23:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.13.5</guid>
    <title>v0.13.5</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.13.5</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Search results now show a snippet of where in the document the term was found</li><li>Slack slash command results also show this snippet! ^</li><li>Improved the ranking of search results</li><li>Added the ability to create a new document from the Starred and Drafts screens</li><li>Added a button to share the document in the header</li><li>When connecting a Slack channel we now post an explanatory message into the channel <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/738">#738</a></li></ul><hr/><p><img alt="search snippets" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/43816984-1e82524c-9a8c-11e8-9eb9-845bbcac0d4f.png"/></p><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to create links to anchors within a document, clicking those links will scroll correctly and not hide the heading behind the top bar.</li><li>Clicking anchors next to headings now copies a link to the clipboard <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/739">#739</a></li><li>There is now a 100 character limit on document titles</li><li>If a document errors while rendering it no longer renders the entire app unusable. We also added more error details to make bug reporting easier. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/737">#737</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 04:50:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.13.4</guid>
    <title>v0.13.4</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.13.4</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Slack integrations can now be set up by users that are authenticated through Google OAuth. Previously If you signed in with Google and then tried to setup an integration it would fail. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/730">#730</a></li><li>Fixed an issue where once a share link had been revoked the same document could not be shared by the same user again. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/733">#733</a></li><li>Fixed the link to developer documentation from the <a href="https://app.getoutline.com/settings/tokens">token settings</a>.</li><li>Fixed a potential JS error when clicking badly formatted links in a document.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 06:47:39 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.13.3</guid>
    <title>v0.13.3</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.13.3</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>This update fixes an important issue where Slack integrations would be associated with the first user in the database. On the hosted version of Outline all of these integrations ended up associated with an inactive test user and have since been purged from the db.</p><p><strong>If you connected Slack since June 3rd 2018 you&#x27;ll need to do so again.</strong></p><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Associate Slack integrations with the correct user (see note above ^)</li><li>Very long document titles now overflow and ellipse correctly everywhere in the UI. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/724">#724</a></li><li>A number of small markdown parsing issues in exceptional situations that could cause a document to fail to render. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/723">#723</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 06:48:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.13.2</guid>
    <title>v0.13.2</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.13.2</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>After duplicating a document you&#x27;ll now be forwarded to the document. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/673">#673</a></li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to change a heading size using markdown shortcuts.</li><li>Downloading documents now works in Firefox. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/692">#692</a></li><li>Shared documents now have the correct mobile styling, much more readable on mobile devices.</li><li>Shared documents could not be loaded while logged into a different Outline team. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/709">#709</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 17:07:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.13.1</guid>
    <title>v0.13.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.13.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixes an issue with the text parsing that could cause paragraphs immediately following an image to be lost upon save.</li><li>Fixes several other parsing issues</li><li>Fixed images having a caption of &quot;undefined&quot; if none is set</li><li>Improved reliability and editor fixes</li><li>Checkboxes now work in Firefox</li><li>Scrolling the sidebar now works in Firefox</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 06:17:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.13.0</guid>
    <title>v0.13.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.13.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>We added the ability to purge your own user account. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/716">#716</a></li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Documents on the dashboard now show the collection they&#x27;re associated with. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/718">#718</a></li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>The signin button in header no longer signs in with Slack by default.</li><li>Fixed the last modified time displayed on document previews is now accurate.</li><li>Fixed an issue that could cause drafts not to save following their initial creation. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/715">#715</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 20:03:03 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.12.0</guid>
    <title>v0.12.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.12.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Documents now display the collection and parent in a new header area. The title also remains on screen as you scroll providing a quick way to jump back to the top of a document.</li></ul><p><img alt="breadcrumb" src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/380914/42140279-495432c6-7d52-11e8-917f-5373ff685186.png"/></p><ul><li>A new, more recognizable, favicon curtesy of <a href="https://twitter.com/maxvoltar">@maxvoltar</a>  </li><li>It&#x27;s now possible to create a new document from the &quot;Home&quot; screen without navigating to a collection first</li><li>We tided up and clarified the save options in a document</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>A number of updates to improve the reliability of the link editing and block insert toolbars. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/707">#707</a></li><li>Fixed an issue that would cause links to other Outline documents (internal links) to not redirect correctly. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/706">#706</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:15:14 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.11.2</guid>
    <title>v0.11.2</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.11.2</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>The editor will now warn you when leaving while images are still pending upload.</li><li>Scroll position is now maintained when entering / leaving editing a document. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/697">#697</a></li><li>The count of drafts is now displayed in the sidebar.</li><li><code>CMD+K</code> now triggers search, the same as Slack. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/671">#671</a></li><li>Inline code blocks are now better formatted. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/698">#698</a></li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li><code>Download</code> option on documents now works from list views such as the homepage. Previously it only worked correctly when the document had been previously viewed.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 17:58:48 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.11.1</guid>
    <title>v0.11.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.11.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li><code>CMD+S</code>, <code>CMD+Enter</code>, <code>Esc</code> keyboard shortcuts now work whether the editor is focused or not instead of triggering the default browser actions</li><li>Improved the styling of inline code blocks</li><li>The copy to clipboard button on code blocks now reads &quot;Copy&quot; instead of &quot;Copied!&quot; by default.</li><li><code>CMD+Enter</code> shortcut now saves and leaves edit mode, as it should</li><li>Fixed an issue where navigating documents could occasionally mark them as modified</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 07:37:50 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.11.0</guid>
    <title>v0.11.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.11.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>We added the ability to export all your data out of Outline. There&#x27;s a new tab under settings &quot;Export Data&quot; and a new option to export all documents for a collection in the overflow menu. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/684">#684</a></li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Now displaying the &quot;joined at&quot; date on the people listing in admin.</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an issue that would display admin options to non-admin users (though they would error with attempted use)</li><li>Squashed an error when uploading images that might result in a &quot;Document failed to save&quot; message. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/685">#685</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 05:47:35 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.10.0</guid>
    <title>v0.10.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.10.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Self-hosted installations can now specify a set of allowed google domains for signin. Account creation outside of this set of domains is disallowed. To setup see the <code>GOOGLE_ALLOWED_DOMAINS</code> env variable <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/blob/master/.env.sample#L23-L25">documentation</a> – thanks to new contributor <a href="https://github.com/satyadeepk">Satyadeep</a> 🎉 <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/681">#681</a></li><li>Share links are now soft deleted, to maintain a record of who created and revoked them.</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an issue that caused newlines to appear on save with deeply nested lists. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/676">#676</a></li><li>Restored table of contents functionality. You&#x27;ll now see a minimal TOC on the right hand side of documents that contain more than one heading to allow quick navigation.</li><li>Fixed an issue that would cause focus in the link toolbar to be lost when autosave triggers <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/674">#674</a></li><li>We improved the handling of document error states when attempting to load documents while offline.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 19:44:26 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.9.0</guid>
    <title>v0.9.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.9.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Added the option to duplicate any document from the overflow (...) menu. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/672">#672</a></li><li>Outline now tracks signin and active times and ip addresses for security and analytics purposes.</li><li>Added toast messages when copying a link so you know that you know it&#x27;s on your clipboard!</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an error if you attempted to connect Slack to a collection and then decided to cancel the operation. We&#x27;ll now show a friendly error message. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/665">#665</a></li><li>Fixed a warning that was showing up when running Outline in development mode. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/667">#667</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 03:45:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.8.1</guid>
    <title>v0.8.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.8.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to paste markdown into the editor from elsewhere and it will be correctly parsed and displayed instead of pasting in text format. <a href="https://github.com/outline/rich-markdown-editor/issues/4">RME #4</a></li><li>Improved spacing on popover menus <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/662">#661</a></li><li>Documents are now only marked as viewed after a few seconds instead of immediately. This should reduce false positives when rapidly clicking through collections.</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Some characters were being displayed as escaped in the document and window titles to a change in the underlying document save format – this is now fixed up. <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/pull/662">#662</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 01:02:12 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.8.0</guid>
    <title>v0.8.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.8.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>We added the ability to sign in to Outline with a Google account, a much requested feature for non-Slack users!</p><p><strong>Note:</strong> If you already sign in with Slack you should continue to do so as the two accounts won&#x27;t be automatically merged. If you&#x27;d like to enable both Google and Slack auth for your team please get in touch at hello@getoutline.com</p><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Further improvements to the settings area, more descriptions and an all-around spruce up</li><li>Moved all OAuth flows to being server-based, now much easier to understand and cuts out a potential point of CSRF.</li><li>Added the ability to update your teams name and logo in the settings</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>An issue that could result in an infinite redirect loop when signing out of Outline.</li><li>A bug that prevented the image cropper from being able to be cancelled.</li><li>A bug that would cause broken images to appear when running Outline in development.</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 21:57:24 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.7.0</guid>
    <title>v0.7.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.7.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>It&#x27;s now possible to create a public share link to documents in your Outline</li><li>We added management in settings to revoke those links</li></ul><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>Tidied the styling in the settings area to bring the various screens inline.</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>An issue with code incorrectly escaping <a href="https://spectrum.chat/outline?thread=4ee55f92-fc54-47c4-bfa1-8e6f7cf7440b">Thread</a></li><li>Link toolbar doesn&#x27;t close when clicking outside of the editor <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/653">#653</a></li><li>Autosave attempts and fails when starting a new document before anything is typed <a href="https://github.com/outline/outline/issues/652">#652</a></li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 03:13:25 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.6.1</guid>
    <title>v0.6.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.6.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Unable to delete draft document when collection is previously deleted</li><li>Failure in documents API endpoint</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 18:09:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.6.0</guid>
    <title>v0.6.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.6.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Added autosave while typing</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Docs with _ and ~ in the title becoming unroutable</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 02:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.5.0</guid>
    <title>v0.5.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.5.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>New Features</h3><p>This release adds the ability to post messages to specific Slack channels when a document is published or updated. We plan that this is the first integration of many to come!</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 04:24:04 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.4.0</guid>
    <title>v0.4.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.4.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>This release updates our paragraph handling to be more inline with other text editors that you&#x27;re used to. Previously there was &quot;padded&quot; area between paragraphs that could not be edited – this is no longer the case.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 06:18:49 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.3.1</guid>
    <title>v0.3.1</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.3.1</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><ul><li>Fixed link toolbar behavior</li><li>Fixed deprecated warnings</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 23:43:17 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.3.0</guid>
    <title>v0.3.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.3.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><h3>Enhancements</h3><ul><li>We added the ability to &quot;Pin&quot; a document to a collection. You can use this to welcome team members, make sure they see the most important documents first, or something else wonderful we haven&#x27;t yet thought of.</li><li>Documents and collections now sort in a more natural order</li></ul><h3>Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed an issue that would cause published drafts not to appear correctly in the collection tree</li></ul></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 07:33:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

  <item>
    <guid>v0.2.0</guid>
    <title>v0.2.0</title>
    <link>https://www.getoutline.com/changelog/v0.2.0</link>
    <description><![CDATA[ <div class="jsx-d6580e98a0d8e617 md" data-reactroot=""><p><br/>This release adds the ability to create and list drafts.</p></div> ]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 08:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>

    </channel>
  </rss>
